Hey, this way?
おーい、こっちか
Please go ahead.
どうぞどうぞ
Sorry.
すいません
The mouth of the bathroom at home broke.
家のお風呂の口が壊れちゃって
Residents?
住人の方?
That's right.
そうなんですよ
Next door to this resident.
この住人の隣の
Can I go home for a while?
ちょっと帰ってもいいですか?
Yes, yes.
はいはい
It's a carrot, but my mouth broke,
人参なんですけど、家の口が壊れちゃって、
It looks like the office is closed as well.
事務所さんもお休みみたいで
Is that so?
そうなんですか?
That's right.
そうなんですよ
No water came out at all.
水が全く出なくて
I'm in trouble.
困っちゃいますね
It's definitely Kowasumiki.
確かにこうわすみきですもんね
That's right.
そうなんですよ
I was wondering if you could help me.
助けてもらえないかなと思って
Well, I don't know if I can do it, but
まぁちょっとできるかどうかわからないですけど、
Will you try it?
やってみます?
Is it true?
本当ですか?
thank you.
ありがとうございます
No, that's outrageous.
いいえ、とんでもないです
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
I can't get in.
入れなくて
Ah, I see.
あ、なるほどですね
You know, I'm going to open this place unexpectedly.
これ ね、意外とここを開けてやるとか、
It's not necessary.
必要ない
Oh, it's out.
お、出た
amazing.
すごい
thank you.
ありがとうございます
No, me too, I've been to the same place before.
いいえ、僕もね、同じ場所、以前やったことあって
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうだったね
It was about 3 months ago, so I kind of remember it.
3ヶ月くらい前に、だからちょっと覚えてたんで
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It seems okay.
大丈夫そうですよね
yes.
はい
Oh, no, that was good.
あ、いやいや、よかったです
Can I get your help if you like?
よかったらお手伝いもらっていいですか?
Ah, no, no, it's okay without making such preparations.
あ、いやいや、そんなお構えなく大丈夫ですよ
please.
ぜひ
Oh, really?
あ、本当ですか?
I had it looked at.
見てもらった
Well then, I apologize for my words.
じゃあお言葉に申し訳ございません
Yes, please come this way.
はい、こっちへどうぞ
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Sorry.
すいません
Oh, sorry.
あ、すいません
I feel so sorry.
なんか申し訳ないですね
No, thank you very much.
いやいや、こちらこそありがとうございます
No, no.
いやいや
Ah, but this is the first time I've met you, Mr. Funari.
あ、でも、ふとなりさん、初めて会いましたね
It's my first time.
初めてですね
thanks so much.
本当にありがとう
No, that's outrageous.
いや、とんでもないです
No, I don't usually have any work to do during this time, so
いや、僕も、この時間帯は普段は仕事不定義だったりするんで、
Sometimes I'm not there.
いなかったりするんですけど
That's right.
そうなんですね
It was good.
よかったです
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなんですか
You're a university student.
大学生さんなんですね
Eh, but you see, I live alone around here quite a bit.
え、でも、あれですね、この辺で結構一人暮らしされてるんです
mosquito?
か?
Sorry, it's something personal.
す いません、なんか個人的なこと
That's right.
そう なんですよ
Do your best at your part-time job.
バイト頑張ってて
Oh, really?
あ、え、本当ですか?
Isn't it difficult?
大変じゃないですか?
It's really difficult.
めっちゃ大変なんですよ
What, what kind of subject are you studying?
え、な、何系を勉強されてるんですか?
I want to study and become a nurse, so I'm studying to be a nurse.
勉強、看護師のなりたくて、看護師の勉強してます
It's tough.
大変だ
There's quite a bit of training and assignments to be done.
結構ね、研修とか課題とかありますね
That's right.
そう なんですよ
It's really hard.
めちゃめちゃ大変です
Oh, that's right.
え、そうなんですね
Eh, part-time job. So, are you working part-time between those classes?
え、アルバイト、じゃあ、その授業の合間アルバイトですか?
I agree.
そうですね
What kind of series are you doing?
何系やってるんですか?
It's food and drink.
飲食です
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Isn't it difficult?
大変じゃないですか?
It's really hard.
めっちゃ大変です
Oh, is that so?
え、そうですか
Well, that's quite true, if you're working part-time,
じゃあ、結構あれですね、アルバイトされてたりすると、
I'm tired and have a lot of trouble.
色々、疲れたりとか、大変ですね、
There were also classes.
授業もあって
I'm very busy, my days are hectic.
めちゃ忙しいんですよね、ごたたたる毎日
Hey, that's right.
へ ー、そうなんだ
I've been busy lately and my body is really stiff.
最近、忙しくて、体めちゃめちゃ凝ってて
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなんですか
Before, I was studying kinesiology, so I was exercising.
前は運動学に入ってたんで、運動してたから、
It was quite soft.
結構柔らかかった
Hey,
へー、
Is that so?
そう なんですか
But, excuse me, but that's really it, isn't it?
でも、失礼ですけど、めっちゃ、あれですよね、
Is it white and stylish?
白くて、スタイルいいですか?
I'm glad it's true.
ほんとですかね、嬉しい
No.
いや ー
Could you please help me stretch for a moment?
ちょっと、ストレッチ手伝ってもらったりできません?
Oh, no, just a little bit, well, yes.
え、いや、ちょっと、まあ、はい
I don't really understand.
よくわかんないんですけど
yes.
はい
May I?
いいですか?
Yes, I would like your help.
はい、手伝ってほしいです
What should I do?
どうしたらいいんですかね?
Wait a minute, is it okay if I get angry?
ちょっと、え、暴っちゃっていいんですか?
yes.
はい
I want you to pat me on the back.
背中を押してほしいです
Yes, I understand.
はい、わかりました
It got hard.
硬くなっちゃった
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんですね
That's right, it got hard.
そうなんですよ、硬くなっちゃった
What did the sports club do?
運動部って何やってたんですか?
I was doing exercise, track and field.
運動、あれしてましたね、陸上
Wow, that's amazing.
へー、すごい
Well, I was really serious about it.
まあ、そんなに、めっちゃガチでやってたわけです
Hey, is that true?
へー、ほんとですか
Really,
めっちゃ、
This time, it's definitely tough.
もう、 今回ですね、やっぱ大変ですね、
That job.
その仕事を
That's right, my body was really pounding.
そうなんですよ、体、めっちゃバキバキになっちゃって
Hey, that's right.
へー、そう
However, I don't really talk to girls this close,
でも、女の人、こうと、こんな近くであまり話すことないんで、
recently.
最近
Sorry, I'm a little nervous.
ちょっと、すいません、ドキドキしちゃって
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Sorry.
すいません
Hey, Vetch, maybe I should do that?
え、ちょっと、ベッチ、 やったほうがいいのかな?
Will your body become softer?
体、柔らかくなりますか?
They say the softer the better.
柔らかいほうがいいって言いますよね
As I continued, it became quite soft.
続けてたら、結構、柔らかくなって
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
This is what I was doing earlier,
さっきやってた、こういう、こういうやつ、
Like this.
こういう
Stretch it like this.
こうやって伸ばしたり
Ah, I see.
あ、なるほど
They say that if you do this every day, you will become weaker.
これの、毎日やってたら、弱くなるって言います
Hey, that's right.
へー、そうなんです
Sorry, I was staring at it.
すいません、じるじる見ちゃって
Eh, something... Eh, no, no, oh...
え、なんか、 え、いやいや、ご、
Sorry, just a moment.
すいません、ちょっと
It's getting bigger.
大きくなってます
No, sorry, um, no.
いや、すいません、あの、いや
I'm fine.
元気なんです
No, it's been a long time since I've had such a close love like this.
いや、 久しぶりに、こんな、近い恋で
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい、すいません
No, not at all.
いや、全然
No, no?
だ、だめですか?
Excuse me for a moment.
そういう、すいません、ちょっと
No, I like it.
いや、好きですよ
Huh, huh? Really?
え、え、ほんとですか?
Oh, I like it.
え、好きって
I think it's good.
いいと思います
Eh, isn't that a bit dangerous?
え、ちょっと、ヤバくないですか?
No, I mean, such a cute girl.
いや、だって、こんな、かわいい子、
It's been a while.
久しぶりですし
I also have quite a few boyfriends.
私もなんか、結構、彼氏いるんですけど、
We're so far away that we can't see each other at all, that's how it is.
遠距離で全然会えなくて、 そうなんです
That's right.
そう なんです よ
No, I just heard something like that.
いや、そんなこと聞いちゃって、ちょっと
No, but it's bad if you have a boyfriend.
いや、でも、彼氏さんいると、まずいですよね
No, not at all, if you didn't say it...
いや、全然、言わなかったら、 え、
What do you mean if you don't say that?
え、え、言わなかったら、 どういうことですか?
I kept it a secret.
内緒にしてた
Eh, eh, I won't find out.
え、え、 バレない
It's getting bigger.
大きくなってる
No, that's what happened.
いや、なっちゃいますよ、それ
They won't find out.
バレないって
ah!
ああ!
It looks really nice on your nails.
爪上めっちゃ綺麗ですね
On the claws.
爪上
So, with your boyfriend at all, at all?
じゃあ、彼氏さんと全然、 全然、
I haven't.
してない
It's hard to see each other.
会えなくて、なかなか
It's busy and difficult.
忙しいし、大変ですね
That's right.
そう なんですよ
It's getting bigger.
大きくなってる
That's what happened.
なっちゃいます、それ
Sorry, just a moment.
すいません、ちょっと
I want to get out.
抜けたい
Well, if I remove it, wouldn't it be bad after all?
いや、抜いたら、やっぱ、まずくないですか?
You can take it out.
抜いてもいいよ
I'll leave it out.
抜かしちゃうね
Huh, huh, huh, huh?
え、 え、え、え、え?
There isn't one.
無いじゃん
It's been a long time, it happened.
めっちゃ、久しぶりだ、そうなった
long time no see?
久しぶり?
long time no see.
久しぶり
Oh, no.
ああ、ダメ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Brother, you were looking at my under eyes and thighs, right?
お兄さん、私の目の下とか、太ももとか見てましたよね?
No, because that's the kind of school I go to.
いや、だってそんな学校してるから
Want to see more?
もっと見たいですか?
Is the station okay?
駅、いいの?
Yeah.
うん
Wow, so beautiful.
うわ、すげえ綺麗
Wow, it's so soft.
すごい、柔らかいね
I'm going to look naughty
エッチな格好しちゃう
hey.
ね
You're very proactive.
積 極的なんですね
Do you hate it?
嫌いですか?
No, Shina, that's fine.
いや、しな、そういうの、いいです
Is it true?
本当ですか?
happy.
嬉しい
How good is that?
なんていいですか?
Lie down.
横になって
Is it true?
ほんとですか?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I think that's enough.
それだけでいっちゃいそう
be patient.
我慢して
Oh, really?
え、本当ですか?
What's the point if I hold back?
我慢したら何かいうことあるの?
There might be.
あるかも
Ya ba.
や ば
Butt.
お尻
Wow, that's amazing.
うわ、すごい
What is this?
何これ?
Something like this.
こんなこと
I want you to lick me.
舐めてもらいたい
舐めてほしいの
No.
ダメ
Not yet.
まだダメ
No.
ダメ
Should I just do it myself?
自分でやるだけなの?
I'll make it a horse.
馬にするよ
What, a lie?
え、嘘?
Wow, that's naughty.
うわ、やらしい
I want you to lick me.
舐めてほしいの
I'm getting excited.
興奮してきちゃった
That's amazing.
すごいね
Wow, so beautiful.
うわ、すごい綺麗
Looks amazing, feels good.
すごいそうだ、気持ちいい
Wow, that's amazing.
うわ、すごい
What's that move?
何 その動き?
Shall I take a look there?
そっち見ようかな
Wow, my legs.
うわ、足が
a.
あ
They're relatives.
親戚だよ
It seems like it will disappear.
消えそう
Okay.
いいよ
I want you to follow me from behind.
後ろからも付いてほしい
Eh, is that okay?
え、いいの?
Wow, I'm hooked.
うわ、まとりつくよ
Wow, it feels good.
うわ、気持ちいい
If you move it too much, it will be damaged.
あんまり動かしたらダメでもいっちゃうから
Yeah.
うん
Wow, it's really narrow.
うわ、すごい狭い
It feels really good.
めっちゃ気持ちいいです
It's true.
ほんとです
Eh, I want you to lick my boobs.
え、おっぱい舐めてほしい
No, I really wanted to see it.
いや、すごい見たかった
Is it okay?
いいんですか?
I want you to lick my tongue too.
舌も舐めてほしい
Is it okay?
いいんですか?
So beautiful.
すごい綺麗
Ah, I think I'll go.
あ、行きそう
Ah, tie it up.
あ、縛る
Feels good.
気持ちいい
picture.
え
Sorry.
すいません
What, will you take responsibility?
え、責任取ってくれるんですか?
Oh, sorry.
え、すいません
It's bad, isn't it?
まずいですよね
Oh, that's amazing.
あ、すごいです
It had been piling up for a while.
ちょっと溜まってたんです
My sister felt so good that I tried my best.
お姉さんが気持ちよすぎて頑張ったんですけど
Please take responsibility.
責任取ってくださいね
Sorry.
すいません